mykidsguide.com 2015-10-30

# Privacy Policy

This blog is a collaborative blog written by a group of individuals.

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This privacy policy sets out how ourfamilyworld.com uses and protects any information that you give MyKidsGuide.com when you use this website.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does contain content which might present a conflict of interest. This content will always be identified.

MyKidsGuide.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

MyKidsGuide.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from June 1st 2010.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Name : First and family name
  * Age and Gender
  * Matrimonial situation and Professional status
  * Number of children
  * Age of children
  * Gender of children
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information that might help us improve our website and provide you with relevant information and offers.

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. We will only send you promotional emails if you agreed and accepted.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

### How we use cookies and beacons

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

We also use third party advertisements on ourfamilyworld.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site.  hese companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type,  time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order  to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically  use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit  [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing /opt_out.asp.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.)

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, you will have the option to choose to receive email offers related to your area of interest. If you don’t want to receive this type of emails, you simply need to click “no” when asked the question.
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for email marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [media@mykidsguide.com](mailto:info@ourfamilyworld.com). You can also choose to use the unsubscribe link available to you on each promotional email you will receive from us.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you offers and promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 22 Oslo, Dollard-des-Ormeaux, Qc, Canada H9A 2H5.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

[MyKidsGuide] is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to  ([amazon.com](http://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Famazon.com%2F&h=sAQH5jPSfAQFHyAYHoW3r7KOJ8KY14ZgInSYAwN85ptQM4w&enc=AZOOoh-7EALVpbu4z5f-du0eCN3Ejo393QyzrC75bzoyTm7smBU3N10itQ6AH-OjWOKZoVRT5ZmwIucdpdFq8DPHbcrQKmUWOSnOYyfoZch2Q8X6lP2HL2thbRjwrZjmjDwDHy36XRTbzDCwa0JQB4n7LEUHU22Sk7j1_K6wMaO8Lbf5Z34wFJuIjpHZ0uNJYMs&s=1) or[myhabit.com](http://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2Fmyhabit.com%2F&h=KAQELXsHYAQEjlSw6G28tIJbglm2zytUU9oyBxTeA3k5bHA&enc=AZOJ4pzbJaHKkt7wQNa2QKOkafsZHbQc4wfge-KoDDKSXWlq6Jv2LafG6FQxy7I-EayIz-hoC4djlMgQ9gLdjWvRgHWkABot99FHcXkqP0smBS_GnoKuj3RYFKafZS2KTVrI-zwA16ZBrWy2hblTkfwhuD-KhwJyV046d6rEvBen4oHO55vDBkeaArHwC5HZWtc&s=1))].” [https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/…/associates/agreement/](https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/gp/associates/agreement/)
